<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MX Mariner</string>
    <string name="app_version">1.1 RC1</string>
    <string name="app_buildno">11212011</string>
    <string name="credits">
Website:\n
MXMariner.com\n\n

Credits:\n
Lead Developer - Will Kamp\n
MatrixMariner.com - manimaul@gmail.com\n\n

Special Thanks:\n
OSMDroid - Nicolas Gramlich\n
OpenCPN - Dave Register\n
GDAL - Frank Warmerdam\n
GDAL Tiler - Klokan Petr Přidal\n
Tiler-Tools - Vadim Shlyakhov\n
GEMF - Allen Budden\n
    </string>
    <string name="nav_warning">MX Mariner software is only a navigational aid. Use MX Mariner software at your own risk.
It displays data for you, but there is no guarantee it is correct, there are many sources for errors.
MX Mariner is not a replacement for navigational knowledge, nor can it navigate by it self.
MX Mariner is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY;
without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
DO NOT rely upon MX Mariner for safety of life or property.\n\n

See License information in the \'Settings\' menu for details.
    </string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright 2011 WILL KAMP All rights reserved.\n\n

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are
permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\n

   1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of
      conditions and the following disclaimer.\n\n

   2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list
      of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials
      provided with the distribution.\n\n

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY WILL KAMP \'\'AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL WILL KAMP OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n\n

The views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the
authors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed
or implied, of WILL KAMP.
    </string>
    <string name="displaymode">Display</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
</resources>
